convore.com 2012-05-01

# Privacy Policy - Grove

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Grove collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Grove's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Grove's visitors use its website. From time to time, Grove may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Grove also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Grove only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Grove's websites choose to interact with Grove in ways that require Grove to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Grove gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [grove.io](https://grove.io/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Grove are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Grove collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Grove. Grove does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Grove may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Grove may monitor the most popular channels on the grove.io site. Grove may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Grove does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Grove discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Grove's behalf or to provide services available at Grove's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Grove's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. **Grove will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.**

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Grove discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Grove believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Grove, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Grove website and have supplied your email address, Grove may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Grove and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Grove takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Grove uses cookies to help Grove identify and track visitors, their usage of Grove website, and their website access preferences. Grove visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Grove's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Grove's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Grove and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Grove may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Grove's sole discretion. Grove encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a grove.io account, you should also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Modified from the [Automattic Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/).

Questions about the Terms of Service should be sent to [team@grove.io](mailto:team@grove.io).

Last updated: September 14, 2011
